Finding Aid for the Ephraim Sales Collection of Tapes and Transcripts of Interviews by Roy Newquist LSC.1494
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Gary, Romain (Writer)., 132 (Box 10)
  - Romain Gary, Lennon Sisters, undated; yrlsc1494_010_132b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:06) (Box 10, Case 132)
- Gary, Romain (Writer)., 141 (Box 11)
  - Romain Gary, Ron Harper, undated; yrlsc1494_011_141a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:31:30) (Box 11, Case 141)
  - Romain Gary, Ron Harper, undated; yrlsc1494_011_141b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:31:35) (Box 11, Case 141)
- Gary, Romain (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.141., (23pp.) (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Gaynor, Janet (Actress)., 27 (Box 2)
  - Janet Gaynor, undated; yrlsc1494_002_027; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:53:04) (Box 2, Case 27)
- Geep, Ellen (Writer)., 161 (Box 11)
- Geis, Bernard (Publisher)., 138 (Box 10)
  - Bernard Geis and Darlene Geis, undated; yrlsc1494_010_138a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:37) (Box 10, Case 138)
  - Bernard Geis and Darlene Geis, undated; yrlsc1494_010_138b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:16:22) (Box 10, Case 138)
- Gibbs, Tony (Writer-editor)., 6 (Box 1)
- Ginsberg, Allen (Writer) -- Transcript., 68; (9pp.) (Box 5)
- Ginsberg, Allen (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.68., (9pp.) (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Girodias, Maurice (Writer)., 176 (Box 12)
  - Maurice Girodias, Mae Mercer, undated; yrlsc1494_012_176a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:21:17) (Box 12, Case 176)
    Content Note: second half of Side A features a live performance by Mae Mercer in Parisian club owned by Maurice Girodias. Content Note: Interview begins on Side B
  - Maurice Girodias, 1963 November 1; yrlsc1494_012_176b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:35:37) (Box 12, Case 176)
- Girodias, Maurice (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.176., (11pp.) (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Gloag, Julian (Writer)., 196 (Box 13)
  - Paul Chevigny, Julian Gloag, undated; yrlsc1494_013_196a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:04:31) (Box 13, Case 196)
- Grizzard, George (Actor)., 188 (Box 13)
  - George Grizzard, undated; yrlsc1494_013_188a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:04:27) (Box 13, Case 188)
- Guess who's coming to dinner (Box 19, Folder 1-7, 10-13)
  - Transcript., (14pp.) (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - A special kind of magic -- Transcript., (6pp.) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - A special kind of magic -- Transcript., (2 copies, each 7pp.) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Glass letter to Newquist., 1967 May 10. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Hepburn, Katherine -- Transcript., (42pp.) (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Hepburn, Katherine -- Transcript., (2 copies, each 21pp.) (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Memo., 1967 May 13. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Merrick, James -- Transcript., (8pp.) (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Press releases. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Tracy, Spencer -- Transcript., (17pp.) (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Volkman, ______ -- Transcript., (7pp.) (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Guthrie, Tyrone (Director)., 166, 173, 175 (Box 12)
  (No transcripts available)
  - Tyrone Guthrie, undated; yrlsc1494_012_175a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:22:48) (Box 12, Case 175)
  - Tyrone Guthrie, undated; yrlsc1494_012_175b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:22:13) (Box 12, Case 175)
- Halsey, William. Editor -- Transcript., (11pp.) (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Hamilton, Donald (Writer) -- Transcript., (3pp.) (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Hargrave, Colleen More (Actress) -- Transcript., (11pp.) (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Harnack, Curt (Writer)., 6 (Box 1)
  - Beulah Roth, Curtis Harnak, Walker Gibbs Jr., 1963 September 1; yrlsc1494_001_006a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:17) (Box 1, Case 6)
    Content Note: features review of Roth's The Cosmopolitan Cat and Harnack's The Work of the Ancient Hand
  - Beulah Roth, Curtis Harnak, Walker Gibbs Jr., 1963 September 1; yrlsc1494_001_006b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:47:32) (Box 1, Case 6)
- Harper, Ron (Actor)., 141 (Box 11)
- Harper, Ron (Actor) -- Transcript of Tape no.141., (14pp.) (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Harris, Julie (Actress)., 151 (Box 11)
  - Julie Harris, 1965 February 1; yrlsc1494_011_151a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:06:35) (Box 11, Case 151)
  - Julie Harris, 1965 February 1; yrlsc1494_011_151b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:06:27) (Box 11, Case 151)
- Hartford, Huntington (Philanthropist)., 163 (Box 12)
  - Huntington Hartford, undated; yrlsc1494_012_163; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:44:00) (Box 12, Case 163)
- Hartford, Huntington (Philanthropist) -- Transcript of Tape no.163., (14pp.) (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Hartman, ______ [Rock producer?]., 37pp.) (Box 16, Folder 26)
- John Hartmann, Chad Stuart, undated; yrlsc1494_007_089a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:33:22) (Box 7, Case 89)
- John Hartmann, Chad Stuart, undated; yrlsc1494_007_089b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:35:07) (Box 7, Case 89)
- Hayes, Helen (Actress)., 177 (Box 12)
  - Helen Hayes, 1965 March 1; yrlsc1494_012_177; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:58:29) (Box 12, Case 177)
- Hecht, Ben (Writer). -- Transcript., 1963 July; (11pp.) (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Hepburn, Katharine [with Spencer Tracy] (Actress and actor)., 63 (Box 5)
  - Spencer Tracy and Katharine Hepburn, undated; yrlsc1494_005_063a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:38:36) (Box 5, Case 63)
  - Spencer Tracy and Katharine Hepburn, undated; yrlsc1494_005_063b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:37:41) (Box 5, Case 63)
- Hepburn, Katherine (Actress)., 91 (Box 7)
  - Katharine Hepburn, undated; yrlsc1494_007_091a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:46:54) (Box 7, Case 91)
  - Katharine Hepburn, undated; yrlsc1494_007_091b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:05:47) (Box 7, Case 91)
- Hepburn, Katherine (Actress)., 1967 June 22.; 197
  Missing.
  Also, See: Guess Who's coming to dinner (Box 19).
- Herblock (Writer)., 149 (Box 11)
  - Herblock, undated; yrlsc1494_011_149; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:29:00) (Box 11, Case 149)
- Heston, Charlton (Actor)., 47 (Box 4)
- Higgins, Trumbull (Writer). -- Transcript., 1963 September; (11pp.) (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Hobson, Laura (Writer)., 168 (Box 12)
  - Laura Z. Hobson, undated; yrlsc1494_012_168; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:59:23) (Box 12, Case 168)
- Hoppe, Art. Columnist. -- Transcript., 1963 September; (9pp.) (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Horne, Lena (Actress) -- Transcript., (3pp.) (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Horne, Lena (Actress)., 115 (Box 9)
  - Lena Horne, undated; yrlsc1494_009_115a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:33:24) (Box 9, Case 115)
  - Lena Horne, undated; yrlsc1494_009_115b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:24:34) (Box 9, Case 115)
- Houghton, Katharine (Actress)., 43 (Box 4)
- Houghton, Katharine (Actress)., 90 (Box 7)
  Also, See: Guess who's coming to dinner (Box 19).
  - Katharine Houghton, undated; yrlsc1494_007_090a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:16) (Box 7, Case 90)
  - Katharine Houghton, undated; yrlsc1494_007_090b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:08:41) (Box 7, Case 90)
- Hunter, Evan (Writer) -- Transcript., (27pp.) (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Hunter, Ross (Film producer)., 108 (Box 8)
  - Ross Hunter, Carol Channing, undated; yrlsc1494_008_108a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:51) (Box 8, Case 108)
  - Ross Hunter, Carol Channing, undated; yrlsc1494_008_108b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:31) (Box 8, Case 108)
- Inge, William (Writer). -- Transcript., 1964 February; (14pp.) (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Isherwood, Christopher (Writer)., 92 (Box 7)
  - Christopher Isherwood, undated; yrlsc1494_007_092a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:50:27) (Box 7, Case 92)
  - Christopher Isherwood, undated; yrlsc1494_007_092b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:34:12) (Box 7, Case 92)
- Jaffe, Rona (Writer)., 67 (Box 5)
- Jaffe, Rona (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.67., (16pp.) (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Jarrett, Kay (Writer) -- Transcript., (3pp.) (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Javonavich, William (Editor)., 10 (Box 1)
- Jewison, Norman (Film producer)., 119 (Box 9)
  - Norman Jewison, Walter Mirisch, Pamela Mason, undated; yrlsc1494_009_119a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:52:46) (Box 9, Case 119)
  - Norman Jewison, Walter Mirisch, Pamela Mason, undated; yrlsc1494_009_119a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:52:42) (Box 9, Case 119)
- Jones, James (Writer)., 94 (Box 7)
  - James Jones, undated; yrlsc1494_007_094a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:45:41) (Box 7, Case 94)
  - James Jones, undated; yrlsc1494_007_094b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:26:16) (Box 7, Case 94)
- Jones, James (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.94., (16pp.) (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Kaminsky, Max (Writer)., 15 (Box 2)
  - Max Kaminsky, undated; yrlsc1494_002_015; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:29:50) (Box 2, Case 15)
    Content Note: features review of My Life in Jazz
- Kaminsky, Max (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.15., (10pp.) (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Kanin, Garson (Writer)., 93 (Box 7)
  - Garson Kanin, undated; yrlsc1494_007_093a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:50:20) (Box 7, Case 93)
  - Garson Kanin, undated; yrlsc1494_007_093b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:53) (Box 7, Case 93)
- Kaye, Danny (Author)., 12 (Box 1)
  - Dannye Kaye, 1965 February 1; yrlsc1494_001_012; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:07) (Box 1, Case 12)
- Keating[?]., 159 (Box 11)
  - Edward M. Keating, undated; yrlsc1494_011_159a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:25:21); Condition Note: audio is intermittently muffled throughout recording (Box 11, Case 159)
  - Edward M. Keating, undated; yrlsc1494_011_159b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:19:28) (Box 11, Case 159)
- Kelly, D. Forest. ______., 134 (Box 10)
- Kidder, Margot (Actress) -- Transcript., (19pp.) (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Kirsch, Robert (Writer)., 48 (Box 4)
- Kirsch, Robert (Writer)., 66 (Box 5)
- Koningsburger, Hans (Writer)., 156 (Box 11)
  - Hans Konigsberger, undated; yrlsc1494_011_156; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:34:31) (Box 11, Case 156)
- Koscina, Sylvia (Actress)., 101 (Box 8)
  - Slyva Koscina, undated; yrlsc1494_008_101; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:51:02) (Box 8, Case 101)
- Koscina, Sylvia (Actress) -- Transcript of Tape no.101., (15pp.) (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Kramer, Karen. ______., 29 (Box 2)
- Kramer, Karen. ______., 145 (Box 11)
- Kramer, Stanley (Film producer) -- Transcript., 43; (45pp.) (Box 4)
- Kramer, Stanley (Film producer)., 58 (Box 5)
  - Stanley Kramer, Anthony Quinn, undated; yrlsc1494_005_058; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:36:56) (Box 5, Case 58)
- Kramer, Stanley (Film producer)., 124 (Box 9)
  - Stanley Kramer, undated; yrlsc1494_009_124a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:48) (Box 9, Case 124)
  - Stanley Kramer, undated; yrlsc1494_009_124b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:03:15) (Box 9, Case 124)
- Kramer, Stanley (Film producer)., 145 (Box 11)
  - Stanley Kramer, Hardy Krüger, Karen Kramer, undated; yrlsc1494_011_145a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:39) (Box 11, Case 145)
    Content Note: features discussion regarding "The Secret of Santa Vittoria'
  - Stanley Kramer, Hardy Krüger, Karen Kramer, undated; yrlsc1494_011_145b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:47:59) (Box 11, Case 145)
- Kramer, Larry, undated; yrlsc1494_005_060b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:00:13) (Box 5, Case 60)
  Content Note: Stanley Kramer's son, Larry, discussing the filming of "The Secret of Santa Vittoria"
- Kreuger, Hardy (Actor)., 62 (Box 5)
  - Stanley Kramer, Hardy Krüger, Robert Crichton, undated; yrlsc1494_005_062a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:33:33) (Box 5, Case 62)
  - Stanley Kramer, Hardy Krüger, Robert Crichton, undated; yrlsc1494_005_062b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:33:33) (Box 5, Case 62)
- Kreuger, Hardy (Actor)., 145 (Box 11)
- Kubly, Herbert (Writer) -- Transcript., (10pp.) (Box 16, Folder 39)
- L'Engle, Madeleine (Writer)., 131 (Box 10)
  - Madeleine L'Engle, Ace Goodman, undated; yrlsc1494_010_131a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:01) (Box 10, Case 131)
  - Madeleine L'Engle, Ace Goodman, undated; yrlsc1494_010_131b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:11) (Box 10, Case 131)
- L'Engle, Madeleine (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.131., (35pp.) (Box 17, Folder 1)
- La Pierre, Dennis (Writer)
  See: Collins, Larry.
- Lasky, Victor. ______., 1 (Box 1)
  - Victor Lasky, Lissa Charell, Jessica Daves, undated; yrlsc1494_001_001; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:38:46) (Box 1, Case 1)
- Lee, Harper (Writer)., 11 (Box 1)
  - Counterpoint: Harper Lee, 1964 June 5; yrlsc1494_001_011; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:11:28) (Box 1, Case 11)
    Content Note: Interview for Counterpoint
- Lehman, Ernest (Writer)., 24 (Box 2)
- Lehman, Ernest (Writer)., 24 (Box 2)
- Lehman, Ernest (Writer)., 80 (Box 6)
  - Ernest Lehman, undated; yrlsc1494_006_080; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:58:07) (Box 6, Case 80)
- Lehman, Ernest (Writer)
- Lemmon, Jack (Actor)., 21 (Box 2)
  - Jack Lemmon, 1964; yrlsc1494_002_021; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:02:14) (Box 2, Case 21)
    Content Note: Interview for The Livley Arts
- Lemmon, Jack (Actor)., 133 (Box 10)
  - Jack Lemmon, undated; yrlsc1494_010_133; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:30:50) (Box 10, Case 133)
- Lennon sisters (Singers) -- Transcript., (5pp.) (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Lennon sisters (Singers)., 29 (Box 3)
  - Stanley Kramer, The Lennon Sisiters, undated; yrlsc1494_003_029a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:37) (Box 3, Case 29)
    Content Note: features interveiws with Stanley Kramer's wife, Karen, actor Renato Racal, and an unidentified man who works on Stanley Kramer's films
  - Stanley Kramer, The Lennon Sisters, undated; yrlsc1494_003_029b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:31:12) (Box 3, Case 29)
- Lennon sisters (Singers)., 96 (Box 7)
  - Peggy and Diane Lennon, undated; yrlsc1494_007_096a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:20) (Box 7, Case 96)
  - Peggy and Diane Lennon, undated; yrlsc1494_007_096b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:15) (Box 7, Case 96)
- Lennon sisters (Singers)., 105 (Box 8)
  - Peggy Lennon of the Lennon Sisters, undated; yrlsc1494_008_105a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:44:31) (Box 8, Case 105)
  - Peggy Lennon of the Lennon Sisters, undated; yrlsc1494_008_105b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:44:16) (Box 8, Case 105)
- Lennon sisters (Singers)., 132 (Box 10)
- Lennon, Danny (Singer)., 51 (Box 4)
  - Danny Lennon, Shirley MacLaine, undated; yrlsc1494_004_051a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:48) (Box 4, Case 51)
  - Danny Lennon, Shirley MacLaine, undated; yrlsc1494_004_051b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:53) (Box 4, Case 51)
- Lernster, Duchess of., 181 (Box 12)
  - Duchess of Leinster, undated; yrlsc1494_012_181a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:52:20) (Box 12, Case 181)
- Lescher, Robert (Editor) -- Transcript., (20pp.) (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Lescher, Robert. Editor. -- Transcript., 1963 December; (18pp.) (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Lessing, Doris (Writer). -- Transcript., 1963 October; (18pp.) (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Liebling, A.J. (Writer). -- Transcript., 1963 December; (15pp.) (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Lillie, Beatrice (Actress)., 48 (Box 4)
  - Beatrice Lillie, Robert Kirsch, undated; yrlsc1494_004_048a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:47:39) (Box 4, Case 48)
  - Beatrice Lillie, Robert Kirsch, undated; yrlsc1494_004_048b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:58:08) (Box 4, Case 48)
- Lillie, Beatrice (Actress) -- Transcript of Tape no.48., (20pp.) (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Lisi, Virna (Actress)., 39 (Box 3)
- Lisi, Virna (Actress)., 117 (Box 9)
  - Virna Lisi, undated; yrlsc1494_009_117a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:44:34); Condition Note: speed increases toward end of recording (Box 9, Case 117)
  - Virna Lisi, undated; yrlsc1494_009_117b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:34) (Box 9, Case 117)
- London, Julie (Singer) -- Transcript., (15pp.) (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Lorant, Stefen (Writer)., 147 (Box 11)
  - Stefan Lorant, undated; yrlsc1494_011_147a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:04:52); Condition Note: loud squeel at end of recording (Box 11, Case 147)
  - Stefan Lorant, undated; yrlsc1494_011_147b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:04:42) (Box 11, Case 147)
- Lorant, Stefen (Writer)., 182 (Box 12)
  - Stefan Lorant, undated; yrlsc1494_012_182a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:04:18) (Box 12, Case 182)
  - Stefan Lorant, undated; yrlsc1494_012_182b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:13:43) (Box 12, Case 182)
- Loy, Myrna (Actress)., 64 (Box 5)
  - Myrna Loy, undated; yrlsc1494_005_064a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:51:23) (Box 5, Case 64)
  - Myrna Loy, undated; yrlsc1494_005_064b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:51:25) (Box 5, Case 64)
- Loy, Myrna (Actress)., 121 (Box 9)
  - Myrna Loy, undated; yrlsc1494_009_121; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:15:03) (Box 9, Case 121)
- Loy, Myrna (Actress)., 122 (Box 9)
  - Myrna Loy, undated; yrlsc1494_009_122; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:54:05) (Box 9, Case 122)
- MacDonald, John (Writer)., 45 (Box 4)
  - Actor with the Guthrie Theater, Newquist's Introduction to 'Counterpoint", John Macdonald, undated; yrlsc1494_004_045a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:28:07) (Box 4, Case 45)
  - Actor with the Guthrie Theater, Newquist's Introduction to 'Counterpoint", John Macdonald, undated; yrlsc1494_004_045b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:33:09) (Box 4, Case 45)
- MacDonald, John (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.45., (16pp.) (Box 17, Folder 10)
- MacDowell, Roddy (Actor)., 41 (Box 3)
  - Roddy McDowell, Warren Beatty, undated; yrlsc1494_003_041a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:33:03) (Box 3, Case 41)
  - Roddy McDowell, Warren Beatty, undated; yrlsc1494_003_041b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:17:33) (Box 3, Case 41)
- MacDowell, Roddy (Actor)., 89 (Box 7)
- MacInnes, Helen (Writer)., 1963 August.; 20 (Box 2)
  - Counterpoint: Helen MacInnes, 1964 May 1; yrlsc1494_002_020; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:10:45) (Box 2, Case 20)
- MacInnes, Helen (Writer). -- Transcript of Tape no.20., 1963 August; (11pp.) (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Macdonald, Dwight (Writer). -- Transcript., 1964 March; (16pp.) (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Maclaine, Shirley (Actress) -- Transcript., (9pp.) (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Maclaine, Shirley (Actress)., 51 (Box 4)
- Maclaine, Shirley (Actress)., 85 (Box 7)
  - Shirley MacLaine, undated; yrlsc1494_007_085a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:59:36) (Box 7, Case 85)
  - Shirley MacLaine, undated; yrlsc1494_007_085b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:59:33) (Box 7, Case 85)
- Magnani, Anna (Actress)., 82 (Box 6)
- Magnani, Anna (Actress)., 136 (Box 10)
  - Anna Magnani, Yvonne Quinn, undated; yrlsc1494_010_136a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:33:49) (Box 10, Case 136)
  - Anna Magnani, Yvonne Quinn, undated; yrlsc1494_010_136b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:28:14) (Box 10, Case 136)
    Content Note: interview with the wife of Sergio Franchi, Yvonne Quinn
- Marvin, Lee (Actor) -- Transcript., (14pp.) (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Marvin, Lee (Actor) -- Transcript., (9pp.) (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Mason, Pamela (Actress)., 46 (Box 4)
  - Pamela Mason, undated; yrlsc1494_004_046a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:52) (Box 4, Case 46)
  - Pamela Mason, undated; yrlsc1494_004_046b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:07) (Box 4, Case 46)
- Mason, Pamela (Actress)., 102 (Box 8)
  - Pamela Mason, Jim Merrick, undated; yrlsc1494_008_102a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:14) (Box 8, Case 102)
  - Pamela Mason, Jim Merrick, undated; yrlsc1494_008_102b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:29) (Box 8, Case 102)
- Mason, Pamela (Actress)., 107 (Box 8)
  - Pamela Mason, Anthony Quinn, undated; yrlsc1494_008_107a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:46:48) (Box 8, Case 107)
  - Pamela Mason, Anthony Quinn, undated; yrlsc1494_008_107b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:58) (Box 8, Case 107)
- Mason, Pamela (Actress)., 119 (Box 9)
- McKuen, Rod (Writer)., 55 (Box 4)
  - Rod McKuen, undated; yrlsc1494_004_055a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:52:42) (Box 4, Case 55)
  - Rod McKuen, undated; yrlsc1494_004_055b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:52:02) (Box 4, Case 55)
- McKuen, Rod (Writer)., 76 (Box 6)
  - Rod McKuen, undated; yrlsc1494_006_076a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:25) (Box 6, Case 76)
  - Rod McKuen, undated; yrlsc1494_006_076b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:26) (Box 6, Case 76)
- Mercouri, Melina (Actress) -- Transcript., (2pp.) (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Merrick, James (Public relations)., 102 (Box 8)
- Merrick, James (Public relations -- Transcript of Tape no.102., (29pp.) (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Miller, Merle - Rhodes, Evan (Writers)., 187 (Box 13)
  - Merle Miller, Evan Rhodes, undated; yrlsc1494_013_187a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:56:09) (Box 13, Case 187)
- Mirisch, Walter (Film producer)., 119 (Box 9)
- Mitford, Jessica (Writer)., 1963 August.; 100 (Box 8)
  - Jessica Mitford, undated; yrlsc1494_008_100; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:11:33) (Box 8, Case 100)
- Mitford, Jessica (Writer). -- Transcript of Tape no.100., 1963 August; (10pp.) (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Moisiewitsch, Tanya (Designer), Guthrie Th., 161 (Box 11)
  - The Tyrone Guthrie Theater, undated; yrlsc1494_011_161a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:04:59) (Box 11, Case 161)
    Content Note: interviews with actors and set designer of the Tyrone Guthrie Theater
  - The Tyrone Guthrie Theater, undated; yrlsc1494_011_161b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:07:31) (Box 11, Case 161)
- Moody, Ralph (Writer)., 28 (Box 2)
  - Commercial for Rand Mcnally, Ralph Moody, undated; yrlsc1494_002_028a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:12) (Box 2, Case 28)
  - Commercial for Rand Mcnally, Ralph Moody, 1963 September 1; yrlsc1494_002_028b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:35:42) (Box 2, Case 28)
- Moore, Mary Tyler (Actress)., 70 (Box 5)
- Moore, Mary Tyler (Actress) -- Transcript of Tape no.70., (19pp.) (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Moorehead, Agnes (Actress)., 98 (Box 7)